How are you today?
今日はどうですか?
white.
白い
It suits you.
似合うじゃん
Does it suit you?
似合う?
Your hair looks like it's been cleaned today.
今日の髪は、清掃な感じだよね
Was it cold?
寒かったのと?
It was cold.
寒かった
expensive?
高い?
expensive.
高い
It's expensive, but make it dry like this.
高いけど、こうやってカラカラして
good?
いい?
Smooth.
すべすべして
That's good.
いいよね
Is that so?
そうかな?
That's right.
そうだよ
Ah, that's out.
あ、それ出たよ
I see.
なるほどね
Don't go out today.
今日は、出かけないで
It's been a while since we met.
会うの久しぶりだもんね
Has anything changed?
変わったことあった?
do not have.
ない
what?
何?
Not anywhere.
どこにない
Where else is it?
他のさ、どこだ?
I didn't say that.
言ってないよ
My butt is soft.
お尻柔らかくて
It's tight.
引き締まってて
Is that so?
そうかな?
I can play it.
弾ける
I don't like it.
嫌
How are you today?
今日はさ、どうですか?
Do you have underwear?
下着てる?
Yeah, combustion.
うん、燃焼
combustion?
燃焼?
combustion.
燃焼
Ah, it's white.
あ、白だ
white.
白
Both black and pink are easy to see.
黒もピンクも見やすい
open?
開ける?
Please.
お願いしー
The bullet is big.
弾大きいな
It's big.
大きいね
cute.
かわいい
How do I apply it?
どうやって塗るの?
picture?
え?
How do I apply it?
どうやって塗るの?
perhaps...
多分...
connect?
繋ぐ?
I guess it's connected.
繋ぐじゃないかな
Sorry, I got the wrong size.
ごめん、サイズ間違えた
I made a mistake.
間違えちゃった
How did you wear it?
どうやって着たの?
It's easy to wear.
着るのが簡単なんだよ
Wrong.
間違った
It's easy to wear.
着るのが簡単なんだよ
I asked him to take his clothes off, but he shouldn't have done this.
脱がしてもらったのに、こいつやっちゃいけないね
sorry.
ごめん
I don't have much power.
結構力が出てない
you do not.
そうしない
I can't take it off.
脱げないよ
It came off.
脱げた
脱 げ た
Cute though.
かわいいけど
Yeah.
うん
It was taken.
取 られた
取られた
appear?
見える?
Can you see it today?
今日も見える?
Yeah.
うん
Head over here?
頭こっち?
Ah, it's transparent.
あ、透けてる
You look like a cute star today too.
今日もかわいい星になってるね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'll keep looking at it.
ずっと眺めてやる
It's very easy to see.
すっごい見やすい
If I have a pussy, I'll let you know.
おまんこがあったら教えてあげる
What kind of face does it have?
どんな顔?
You can also see the back side.
裏顔も眺めてくれる
Awesome
すっごい
hey.
ね
It's going to be a great view today.
今日は すごい眺めてくれるね
Because it's been a while.
久々だから
Yeah.
うん
To the pussy.
おまんこさまに
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I haven't done sharti.
シャーティしてないよ
Haven't you done Shati?
シャーティしてない?
Weird.
変な
It tastes kind of weird.
なんか変な味する
Were you playing sharti?
シャーティしてた?
Yeah.
うん
I did it.
しちゃった
Germany in China looks good.
中国のドイツよく見える
appear?
見える?
Is it warm?
あったかいの?
Warm.
あったかい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
There are toys too.
おもちゃもあるんだけど
Yeah.
うん
Feel good.
気持ちよく
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
How about this?
これどうか
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Didn't it hurt?
痛くなかった?
It's not good.
良くないよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It's ringing.
鳴ってるよ
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
Is that so?
そういうこと?
It's salt, right?
塩でしょ
salt?
塩?
I ran out of salt.
塩ふいちゃった